<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Huntington Underwriting Limited</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Huntington Underwriting Limited</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Huntington Underwriting Limited (“HUL”) is an international (re)insurance Underwriting Manager based in the Labuan International Business and Financial Centre. It is an associate of the Singapore-headquartered insurance services group, Huntington Group Pte Ltd.
Incorporated (Company No. LL09214) in the Malaysian Federal Territory of Labuan under the Labuan Companies Act 1990, HUL is licensed (Licence No. US201226) by The Labuan Financial Services Authority as a Labuan Underwriting Manager under the Labuan Financial Services &amp;amp; Securities Act 2010.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Huntington Underwriting Limited Principal Officer Anthony Egerton aegerton@huntingtonunderwriting.com
Chief Financial Officer Gerard L. Pennefather gpennefather@huntingtonunderwriting.com
Compliance Officer Iain Herbert
iherbert@huntingtonunderwriting.com
Operations and Claims Cheung Ngai Kay
nkcheung@huntingtonunderwriting.com
Address Brighton Place, U0215, Jalan Bahasa, PO Box 80431,87014 Labuan FT, Malaysia
Tel: +6087 442899
Fax: +6087 451899
Incorporated in the Federal Territory of Labuan, Malaysia
(Company No: LL09214)
Authorised and Regulated by the Labuan Financial Services Authority
(Licence No: US201226)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Huntington Underwriting Limited and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regulation</title>
      <link>/regulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/regulation/</guid>
      <description>Labuan Financial Services Authority Huntington Underwriting Limited (formerly known as AIH Underwriting Limited, “HUL”) is a Labuan Underwriting Manager licensed by the Labuan Financial Services Authority under the Labuan Financial Services &amp;amp; Securities Act 2010 in Malaysia: Licence Number US201226
Brighton Management Limited Brighton Management Limited is the appointed insurance manager for HUL.
Kensington Trust Labuan Limited Kensington Trust Labuan Limited is the appointed Trust Company for HUL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured Solutions</title>
      <link>/structured/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/structured/</guid>
      <description>Huntington Underwriting Limited operates an underwriting facility for Structured Solutions on behalf of international reinsurer(s) with a minimum financial strength rating of A- (Excellent) by AM Best.
Structured Solutions are bespoke, non-traditional (re)insurance programmes that help manage the volatility in ‘baskets’ of risks, often over several years, incorporating aggregate limits of liability and rewarding underwriting profitability. Frequent use is made of funds withheld arrangements/premium reserve deposits to help minimise frictional costs and reduce foreign currency exchange risks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>